I have reviewed so many crochet bags in
the past. I have tried so many crochet
bags. I've gotten so many crochet bags
for Christmas
and every time I get a crochet bag and
look at it, I'm like, "This is amazing.
This fixes all my problems. I'm obsessed
with this. I love it."
Why don't I use them? Why do I always
still just grab a tote bag every time I
need to travel with a project? I'm just
grabbing your most basic tote bag even
though I have all of these like really,
really, really nice crochet bags. So,
this time whenever I was looking for
items to review, I found something that
was marketed as a crochet bag tote.
And I'm curious if I would be more
likely to carry a specific crochet
[music] bag if it was a little bit just
more